# -*- coding: utf-8 -*-
#
# Copyright (C) 2021 Max-Planck-Gesellschaft zur Förderung der Wissenschaften e.V. (MPG),
# acting on behalf of its Max Planck Institute for Intelligent Systems and the
# Max Planck Institute for Biological Cybernetics. All rights reserved.
#
# Max-Planck-Gesellschaft zur Förderung der Wissenschaften e.V. (MPG) is holder of all proprietary rights
# on this computer program. You can only use this computer program if you have closed a license agreement
# with MPG or you get the right to use the computer program from someone who is authorized to grant you that right.
# Any use of the computer program without a valid license is prohibited and liable to prosecution.
# Contact: ps-license@tuebingen.mpg.de
#
# If you use this code in a research publication please cite the following:
#
# @conference{AMASS:ICCV:2019,
#   title = {{AMASS}: Archive of Motion Capture as Surface Shapes},
#   author = {Mahmood, Naureen and Ghorbani, Nima and Troje, Nikolaus F. and Pons-Moll, Gerard and Black, Michael J.},
#   booktitle = {International Conference on Computer Vision},
#   pages = {5442--5451},
#   month = oct,
#   year = {2019},
#   month_numeric = {10}
# }
#
# You can find complementary content at the project website: https://amass.is.tue.mpg.de/
#
# Code Developed by:
# Nima Ghorbani <https://nghorbani.github.io/>
# Naureen Mahmood <https://ps.is.tuebingen.mpg.de/person/nmahmood>
# Matthew Loper <https://ps.is.mpg.de/~mloper>
# While at Max-Planck Institute for Intelligent Systems, Tübingen, Germany
#
# 2021.06.18
general_labels_map = {'HEAD_TOP': 'ARIEL',
                      'TOPBACK': 'C7',
                      'NECK_BASE': 'C7',
                      'CHEST': 'CLAV',
                      'UPTHRX': 'CLAV',
                      'L_ANKLE': 'LANK',
                      'L_ANK': 'LANK',
                      'L_UPBACK': 'LBAK',
                      'LBAC': 'LBAK',
                      'LBAC-1': 'LBAK',
                      'L_BICEP': 'LBCEP',
                      'L_EAR': 'LBHD',
                      'NEWLSHO': 'LBCEP',
                      'NEWRSHO': 'RBCEP',
                      'NEWLBAC': 'LNWST',
                      'NEWRBAC': 'RNWST',
                      'LBSHO': 'LBSH',
                      'L_B_SHOULDER': 'LBSH',
                      'L_B_WAIST': 'LBWT',
                      'L_BWT': 'LBWT',
                      'LPSI': 'LBWT',
                      'L_CALF': 'LCLF',
                      'LIBH': 'LEBHI',
                      'LMBH': 'LEBHM',
                      'LPBH': 'LEBHP',
                      'LRBH': 'LEBHR',
                      'LIDIP': 'LEIDIP',
                      'L_ELBOW': 'LELB',
                      'L_INELBOW': 'LELBIN',
                      'LILB': 'LELBIN',
                      'LIEL': 'LELBIN',
                      'LMDIP': 'LEMDIP',
                      'LPDIP': 'LEPDIP',
                      'LPPIP': 'LEPPIP',
                      'LPTIP': 'LEPTIP',
                      'LRDIP': 'LERDIP',
                      'LRPIP': 'LERPIP',
                      'LRTIP': 'LERTIP',
                      'LTMP': 'LETMP',
                      'LTPIPI': 'LETPIPIN',
                      'LTPIPO': 'LTHM4',
                      'HEAD_OFFSET': 'LFHD',
                      'L_PINKY': 'LFIN',
                      'LOHAND': 'LFIN',
                      'L_FIN': 'LFIN',
                      'LPHLX5': 'LFIN',
                      'L_FOREARM': 'LFRM',
                      'LARM': 'LFRM',
                      'LFRA': 'LFRM',
                      'LWRE': 'LFRM',
                      'LWRI': 'LFRMIN',
                      'L_F_SHOULDER': 'LFSH',
                      'LASI': 'LFWT',
                      'L_F_WAIST': 'LFWT',
                      'L_FWT': 'LFWT',
                      'L_HEEL': 'LHEE',
                      'LHEL': 'LHEE',
                      'LANKIN': 'LHEEI',
                      'LANKI': 'LHEEI',
                      'LIPIP': 'LIDX1',
                      'LEIPIP': 'LIDX1',
                      'LITIP': 'LIDX3',
                      'LEITIP': 'LIDX3',
                      'L_INWRIST': 'LIWR',
                      'LWRA': 'LIWR',
                      'LWRST': 'LIWR',
                      'L_OUTKNEE': 'LKNE',
                      'L_KNEE': 'LKNE',
                      'L_INKNEE': 'LKNI',
                      'LKNEIN': 'LKNI',
                      'LMPIP': 'LMID1',
                      'LEMPIP': 'LMID1',
                      'LMTIP': 'LMID3',
                      'LEMTIP': 'LMID3',
                      'L_BIGTOE': 'LMT1',
                      'L_PINKYTOE': 'LMT5',
                      'L_OUTWRIST': 'LOWR',
                      'LWRB': 'LOWR',
                      'L_WRIST': 'LOWR',
                      # 'LEPTIP': 'LPNK3',
                      'LMWT': 'LPRFWT',
                      'LTOE5': 'LRSTBEEF',
                      'L_MIDBACK': 'LSCAP',
                      'L_SHIN': 'LSHN',
                      'LSHIN': 'LSHN',
                      'L_SHOULDER': 'LSHOUP',
                      'LHIP': 'LTHI',
                      'L_HIP': 'LTHI',
                      'L_HAM': 'LTHI',
                      'L_THIGH': 'LTHILO',
                      'LTHIGH': 'LTHILO',
                      'LTTIP': 'LTHM3',
                      # 'LETTIP': 'LTHM3',
                      'L_THUMB': 'LTHMB',
                      'LIHAND': 'LTHMB',
                      'LPHLX1': 'LTHMB',
                      'LLEG': 'LTIB',
                      'L_TOETIP': 'LTOE',
                      'LTOE1': 'LTOE',
                      'L_TRICEP': 'LUPA',
                      'R_ANKLE': 'RANK',
                      'R_ANK': 'RANK',
                      'R_UPBACK': 'RBAK',
                      'RBAC': 'RBAK',
                      'RBAC-1': 'RBAK',
                      'R10': 'RBAK',
                      'OFFSET': 'RBAK',
                      'R_BICEP': 'RBCEP',
                      'R_EAR': 'RBHD',
                      'RBSHO': 'RBSH',
                      'R_B_SHOULDER': 'RBSH',
                      'RPSI': 'RBWT',
                      'R_B_WAIST': 'RBWT',
                      'R_BWT': 'RBWT',
                      'R_CALF': 'RCLF',
                      'R_ELBOW': 'RELB',
                      'R_INELBOW': 'RELBIN',
                      'RILB': 'RELBIN',
                      'RIEL': 'RELBIN',
                      'R_PINKY': 'RFIN',
                      'ROHAND': 'RFIN',
                      'R_FIN': 'RFIN',
                      'RPHLX5': 'RFIN',
                      'R_FOREARM': 'RFRM',
                      'RARM': 'RFRM',
                      'RFRA': 'RFRM',
                      'RWRE': 'RFRM',
                      'RWRI': 'RFRMIN',
                      'R_F_SHOULDER': 'RFSH',
                      'RASI': 'RFWT',
                      'R_F_WAIST': 'RFWT',
                      'R_FWT': 'RFWT',
                      'R_HEEL': 'RHEE',
                      'RHEL': 'RHEE',
                      'RANKIN': 'RHEEI',
                      'RANKI': 'RHEEI',
                      'RIBH': 'RIBHI',
                      'RMBH': 'RIBHM',
                      'RPBH': 'RIBHP',
                      'RRBH': 'RIBHR',
                      'RITIP': 'RIDX3',
                      'RIITIP': 'RIDX3',
                      'RIDIP': 'RIIDIP',
                      'RIPIP': 'RIIPIP',
                      'RMDIP': 'RIMDIP',
                      'RMPIP': 'RIMPIP',
                      'RPDIP': 'RIPDIP',
                      'RPPIP': 'RIPPIP',
                      'RRDIP': 'RIRDIP',
                      'RRPIP': 'RIRPIP',
                      'RTMP': 'RITMP',
                      'RTPIPI': 'RITPIPIN',
                      'RTPIPO': 'RITPIPOUT',
                      'RTTIP': 'RITTIP',
                      'R_INWRIST': 'RIWR',
                      'RWRA': 'RIWR',
                      'R_OUTKNEE': 'RKNE',
                      'R_KNEE': 'RKNE',
                      'R_INKNEE': 'RKNI',
                      'RKNEIN': 'RKNI',
                      'RMTIP': 'RMID3',
                      'RIMTIP': 'RMID3',
                      'R_BIGTOE': 'RMT1',
                      'R_PINKYTOE': 'RMT5',
                      'R_OUTWRIST': 'ROWR',
                      'RWRB': 'ROWR',
                      'R_WRIST': 'ROWR',
                      'RPTIP': 'RPNK3',
                      'RIPTIP': 'RPNK3',
                      'RMWT': 'RPRFWT',
                      'RRTIP': 'RRNG3',
                      'RIRTIP': 'RRNG3',
                      'RTOE5': 'RRSTBEEF',
                      'R_MIDBACK': 'RSCAP',
                      'R_SHIN': 'RSHN',
                      'RSHIN': 'RSHN',
                      'R_SHOULDER': 'RSHOUP',
                      'RHIP': 'RTHI',
                      'R_HIP': 'RTHI',
                      'R_HAM': 'RTHI',
                      'R_THIGH': 'RTHILO',
                      'RTHIGH': 'RTHILO',
                      'R_THUMB': 'RTHMB',
                      'RIHAND': 'RTHMB',
                      'RPHLX1': 'RTHMB',
                      'RLEG': 'RTIB',
                      'R_TOETIP': 'RTOE',
                      'RTOE1': 'RTOE',
                      'R_TRICEP': 'RUPA',
                      'STERNUM': 'STRN',
                      'SETRNUM': 'STRN',
                      'LOTHRX': 'STRN',
                      'LOBACK': 'T10',
                      'MIDBACK': 'T8',
                      'MID_BACK': 'T8',
                      'ghost': 'nan',
                      'NaN': 'nan',
                    
                        # "Skeleton1ChestHFront": "CLAV",
                        # "Skeleton1ChestLFront": "STRN",
                        # "Skeleton1ChestHBack": "C7",
                        # "Skeleton1ChestLBack": "T10",

                        # "Skeleton1HeadRFront": "RFHD",
                        # "Skeleton1HeadRBack": "RBHD",
                        # "Skeleton1HeadTop": "ARIEL",
                        # "Skeleton1HeadLFront": "LFHD",
                        # "Skeleton1HeadLBack": "LBHD",

                        # "Skeleton1WaistRFront": "RFWT",
                        # "Skeleton1WaistLFront": "LFWT",
                        # "Skeleton1WaistMFront": "MFWT",
                        # "Skeleton1WaistRBack": "RBWT",
                        # "Skeleton1WaistLBack": "LBWT",
                        # "Skeleton1WaistMBack": "MBWT",
                        
                        # "Skeleton1RShoulderFront": "RFSH",
                        # "Skeleton1RShoulderBack": "RBSH",
                        # "Skeleton1LShoulderFront": "LFSH",
                        # "Skeleton1LShoulderBack": "LBSH",
                        # "Skeleton1RArm": "RUPA",
                        # "Skeleton1LArm": "LUPA",
                        # "Skeleton1RForeArm": "RFRM",
                        # "Skeleton1LForeArm": "LFRM",
                        # "Skeleton1RElbowHigh": "RELB",
                        # "Skeleton1RElbowLow": "RELBIN",
                        # "Skeleton1LElbowHigh": "LELB",
                        # "Skeleton1LElbowLow": "LELBIN",
                        # "Skeleton1RWristIn": "RIWR",
                        # "Skeleton1RWristOut": "ROWR",
                        # "Skeleton1LWristIn": "LIWR",
                        # "Skeleton1LWristOut": "LOWR",

                        # "Skeleton1RHandIn": "RTHMB",
                        # "Skeleton1RHandOut": "RFIN",
                        # "Skeleton1LHandIn": "LTHMB",
                        # "Skeleton1LHandOut": "LFIN",
                        # "Skeleton1LThigh": "LTHI",
                        # "Skeleton1RThigh": "RTHI",
                        # "Skeleton1LShin": "LSHN",
                        # "Skeleton1RShin": "RSHN",
                        # "Skeleton1LKneeOut": "LKNE",
                        # "Skeleton1LKneeIn": "LKNI",
                        # "Skeleton1RKneeOut": "RKNE",
                        # "Skeleton1RKneeIn": "RKNI",
                        # "Skeleton1LAnkleOut": "LANK",
                        # "Skeleton1RAnkleOut": "RANK",
                        # "Skeleton1RHeel": "RHEE",
                        # "Skeleton1LHeel": "LHEE",
                        # "Skeleton1LToeTip": "LTOE",
                        # "Skeleton1LToeIn": "LMT1",
                        # "Skeleton1LToeOut": "LMT5",
                        # "Skeleton1RToeTip": "RTOE",
                        # "Skeleton1RToeIn": "RMT1",
                        # "Skeleton1RToeOut": "RMT5",

                        'Skeleton4ChestLow': 'SkeletonChestLow',
                        'Skeleton4ChestTop': 'SkeletonChestTop',
                        'Skeleton4WaistRFront': 'SkeletonWaistRFront',
                        'Skeleton4WaistLFront': 'SkeletonWaistLFront',
                        'Skeleton4WaistLBack': 'SkeletonWaistLBack',
                        'Skeleton4WaistRBack': 'SkeletonWaistRBack',
                        'Skeleton4WaistCBack': 'SkeletonWaistCBack',
                        'Skeleton4BackLeft': 'SkeletonBackLeft',
                        'Skeleton4BackRight': 'SkeletonBackRight',
                        'Skeleton4LShoulderBack': 'SkeletonLShoulderBack',
                        'Skeleton4RShoulderBack': 'SkeletonRShoulderBack',
                        'Skeleton4BackTop': 'SkeletonBackTop',
                        'Skeleton4HeadFront': 'SkeletonHeadFront',
                        'Skeleton4HeadTop': 'SkeletonHeadTop',
                        'Skeleton4HeadRight':'SkeletonHeadRight',
                        'Skeleton4HeadLeft': 'SkeletonHeadLeft',
                        'Skeleton4RShoulderTop': 'SkeletonRShoulderTop',
                        'Skeleton4RUArmHigh': 'SkeletonRUArmHigh',
                        'Skeleton4RElbowOut': 'SkeletonRElbowOut',
                        'Skeleton4RFArm': 'SkeletonRFArm',
                        'Skeleton4RWristIn': 'SkeletonRWristIn',
                        'Skeleton4RWristOut': 'SkeletonRWristOut',
                        'Skeleton4RHandIn': 'SkeletonRHandIn',
                        'Skeleton4RHandOut': 'SkeletonRHandOut',
                        'Skeleton4LShoulderTop': 'SkeletonLShoulderTop',
                        'Skeleton4LUArmHigh': 'SkeletonLUArmHigh',
                        'Skeleton4LElbowOut': 'SkeletonLElbowOut',
                        'Skeleton4LFArm': 'SkeletonLFArm',
                        'Skeleton4LWristIn': 'SkeletonLWristIn',
                        'Skeleton4LWristOut': 'SkeletonLWristOut',
                        'Skeleton4LHandIn': 'SkeletonLHandIn',
                        'Skeleton4LHandOut': 'SkeletonLHandOut',
                        'Skeleton4RThighFront': 'SkeletonRThighFront',
                        'Skeleton4RThighSide': 'SkeletonRThighSide',
                        'Skeleton4RKneeOut': 'SkeletonRKneeOut',
                        'Skeleton4RShin': 'SkeletonRShin',
                        'Skeleton4RAnkleOut': 'SkeletonRAnkleOut',
                        'Skeleton4RToeTip': 'SkeletonRToeTip',
                        'Skeleton4RToeIn': 'SkeletonRToeIn',
                        'Skeleton4RToeOut': 'SkeletonRToeOut',
                        'Skeleton4RHeel': 'SkeletonRHeel',
                        'Skeleton4LThighFront': 'SkeletonLThighFront',
                        'Skeleton4LThighSide': 'SkeletonLThighSide',
                        'Skeleton4LKneeOut': 'SkeletonLKneeOut',
                        'Skeleton4LShin': 'SkeletonLShin',
                        'Skeleton4LAnkleOut': 'SkeletonLAnkleOut',
                        'Skeleton4LToeTip': 'SkeletonLToeTip',
                        'Skeleton4LToeIn': 'SkeletonLToeIn',
                        'Skeleton4LToeOut': 'SkeletonLToeOut',
                        'Skeleton4LHeel': 'SkeletonLHeel',

                        'Skeleton8ChestLow': 'SkeletonChestLow',
                        'Skeleton8ChestTop': 'SkeletonChestTop',
                        'Skeleton8WaistRFront': 'SkeletonWaistRFront',
                        'Skeleton8WaistLFront': 'SkeletonWaistLFront',
                        'Skeleton8WaistLBack': 'SkeletonWaistLBack',
                        'Skeleton8WaistRBack': 'SkeletonWaistRBack',
                        'Skeleton8WaistCBack': 'SkeletonWaistCBack',
                        'Skeleton8BackLeft': 'SkeletonBackLeft',
                        'Skeleton8BackRight': 'SkeletonBackRight',
                        'Skeleton8LShoulderBack': 'SkeletonLShoulderBack',
                        'Skeleton8RShoulderBack': 'SkeletonRShoulderBack',
                        'Skeleton8BackTop': 'SkeletonBackTop',
                        'Skeleton8HeadFront': 'SkeletonHeadFront',
                        'Skeleton8HeadTop': 'SkeletonHeadTop',
                        'Skeleton8HeadRight':'SkeletonHeadRight',
                        'Skeleton8HeadLeft': 'SkeletonHeadLeft',
                        'Skeleton8RShoulderTop': 'SkeletonRShoulderTop',
                        'Skeleton8RUArmHigh': 'SkeletonRUArmHigh',
                        'Skeleton8RElbowOut': 'SkeletonRElbowOut',
                        'Skeleton8RFArm': 'SkeletonRFArm',
                        'Skeleton8RWristIn': 'SkeletonRWristIn',
                        'Skeleton8RWristOut': 'SkeletonRWristOut',
                        'Skeleton8RHandIn': 'SkeletonRHandIn',
                        'Skeleton8RHandOut': 'SkeletonRHandOut',
                        'Skeleton8LShoulderTop': 'SkeletonLShoulderTop',
                        'Skeleton8LUArmHigh': 'SkeletonLUArmHigh',
                        'Skeleton8LElbowOut': 'SkeletonLElbowOut',
                        'Skeleton8LFArm': 'SkeletonLFArm',
                        'Skeleton8LWristIn': 'SkeletonLWristIn',
                        'Skeleton8LWristOut': 'SkeletonLWristOut',
                        'Skeleton8LHandIn': 'SkeletonLHandIn',
                        'Skeleton8LHandOut': 'SkeletonLHandOut',
                        'Skeleton8RThighFront': 'SkeletonRThighFront',
                        'Skeleton8RThighSide': 'SkeletonRThighSide',
                        'Skeleton8RKneeOut': 'SkeletonRKneeOut',
                        'Skeleton8RShin': 'SkeletonRShin',
                        'Skeleton8RAnkleOut': 'SkeletonRAnkleOut',
                        'Skeleton8RToeTip': 'SkeletonRToeTip',
                        'Skeleton8RToeIn': 'SkeletonRToeIn',
                        'Skeleton8RToeOut': 'SkeletonRToeOut',
                        'Skeleton8RHeel': 'SkeletonRHeel',
                        'Skeleton8LThighFront': 'SkeletonLThighFront',
                        'Skeleton8LThighSide': 'SkeletonLThighSide',
                        'Skeleton8LKneeOut': 'SkeletonLKneeOut',
                        'Skeleton8LShin': 'SkeletonLShin',
                        'Skeleton8LAnkleOut': 'SkeletonLAnkleOut',
                        'Skeleton8LToeTip': 'SkeletonLToeTip',
                        'Skeleton8LToeIn': 'SkeletonLToeIn',
                        'Skeleton8LToeOut': 'SkeletonLToeOut',
                        'Skeleton8LHeel': 'SkeletonLHeel',

                        'Skeleton9ChestLow': 'SkeletonChestLow',
                        'Skeleton9ChestTop': 'SkeletonChestTop',
                        'Skeleton9WaistRFront': 'SkeletonWaistRFront',
                        'Skeleton9WaistLFront': 'SkeletonWaistLFront',
                        'Skeleton9WaistLBack': 'SkeletonWaistLBack',
                        'Skeleton9WaistRBack': 'SkeletonWaistRBack',
                        'Skeleton9WaistCBack': 'SkeletonWaistCBack',
                        'Skeleton9BackLeft': 'SkeletonBackLeft',
                        'Skeleton9BackRight': 'SkeletonBackRight',
                        'Skeleton9LShoulderBack': 'SkeletonLShoulderBack',
                        'Skeleton9RShoulderBack': 'SkeletonRShoulderBack',
                        'Skeleton9BackTop': 'SkeletonBackTop',
                        'Skeleton9HeadFront': 'SkeletonHeadFront',
                        'Skeleton9HeadTop': 'SkeletonHeadTop',
                        'Skeleton9HeadRight':'SkeletonHeadRight',
                        'Skeleton9HeadLeft': 'SkeletonHeadLeft',
                        'Skeleton9RShoulderTop': 'SkeletonRShoulderTop',
                        'Skeleton9RUArmHigh': 'SkeletonRUArmHigh',
                        'Skeleton9RElbowOut': 'SkeletonRElbowOut',
                        'Skeleton9RFArm': 'SkeletonRFArm',
                        'Skeleton9RWristIn': 'SkeletonRWristIn',
                        'Skeleton9RWristOut': 'SkeletonRWristOut',
                        'Skeleton9RHandIn': 'SkeletonRHandIn',
                        'Skeleton9RHandOut': 'SkeletonRHandOut',
                        'Skeleton9LShoulderTop': 'SkeletonLShoulderTop',
                        'Skeleton9LUArmHigh': 'SkeletonLUArmHigh',
                        'Skeleton9LElbowOut': 'SkeletonLElbowOut',
                        'Skeleton9LFArm': 'SkeletonLFArm',
                        'Skeleton9LWristIn': 'SkeletonLWristIn',
                        'Skeleton9LWristOut': 'SkeletonLWristOut',
                        'Skeleton9LHandIn': 'SkeletonLHandIn',
                        'Skeleton9LHandOut': 'SkeletonLHandOut',
                        'Skeleton9RThighFront': 'SkeletonRThighFront',
                        'Skeleton9RThighSide': 'SkeletonRThighSide',
                        'Skeleton9RKneeOut': 'SkeletonRKneeOut',
                        'Skeleton9RShin': 'SkeletonRShin',
                        'Skeleton9RAnkleOut': 'SkeletonRAnkleOut',
                        'Skeleton9RToeTip': 'SkeletonRToeTip',
                        'Skeleton9RToeIn': 'SkeletonRToeIn',
                        'Skeleton9RToeOut': 'SkeletonRToeOut',
                        'Skeleton9RHeel': 'SkeletonRHeel',
                        'Skeleton9LThighFront': 'SkeletonLThighFront',
                        'Skeleton9LThighSide': 'SkeletonLThighSide',
                        'Skeleton9LKneeOut': 'SkeletonLKneeOut',
                        'Skeleton9LShin': 'SkeletonLShin',
                        'Skeleton9LAnkleOut': 'SkeletonLAnkleOut',
                        'Skeleton9LToeTip': 'SkeletonLToeTip',
                        'Skeleton9LToeIn': 'SkeletonLToeIn',
                        'Skeleton9LToeOut': 'SkeletonLToeOut',
                        'Skeleton9LHeel': 'SkeletonLHeel',

                        'Skeleton10ChestLow': 'SkeletonChestLow',
                        'Skeleton10ChestTop': 'SkeletonChestTop',
                        'Skeleton10WaistRFront': 'SkeletonWaistRFront',
                        'Skeleton10WaistLFront': 'SkeletonWaistLFront',
                        'Skeleton10WaistLBack': 'SkeletonWaistLBack',
                        'Skeleton10WaistRBack': 'SkeletonWaistRBack',
                        'Skeleton10WaistCBack': 'SkeletonWaistCBack',
                        'Skeleton10BackLeft': 'SkeletonBackLeft',
                        'Skeleton10BackRight': 'SkeletonBackRight',
                        'Skeleton10LShoulderBack': 'SkeletonLShoulderBack',
                        'Skeleton10RShoulderBack': 'SkeletonRShoulderBack',
                        'Skeleton10BackTop': 'SkeletonBackTop',
                        'Skeleton10HeadFront': 'SkeletonHeadFront',
                        'Skeleton10HeadTop': 'SkeletonHeadTop',
                        'Skeleton10HeadRight':'SkeletonHeadRight',
                        'Skeleton10HeadLeft': 'SkeletonHeadLeft',
                        'Skeleton10RShoulderTop': 'SkeletonRShoulderTop',
                        'Skeleton10RUArmHigh': 'SkeletonRUArmHigh',
                        'Skeleton10RElbowOut': 'SkeletonRElbowOut',
                        'Skeleton10RFArm': 'SkeletonRFArm',
                        'Skeleton10RWristIn': 'SkeletonRWristIn',
                        'Skeleton10RWristOut': 'SkeletonRWristOut',
                        'Skeleton10RHandIn': 'SkeletonRHandIn',
                        'Skeleton10RHandOut': 'SkeletonRHandOut',
                        'Skeleton10LShoulderTop': 'SkeletonLShoulderTop',
                        'Skeleton10LUArmHigh': 'SkeletonLUArmHigh',
                        'Skeleton10LElbowOut': 'SkeletonLElbowOut',
                        'Skeleton10LFArm': 'SkeletonLFArm',
                        'Skeleton10LWristIn': 'SkeletonLWristIn',
                        'Skeleton10LWristOut': 'SkeletonLWristOut',
                        'Skeleton10LHandIn': 'SkeletonLHandIn',
                        'Skeleton10LHandOut': 'SkeletonLHandOut',
                        'Skeleton10RThighFront': 'SkeletonRThighFront',
                        'Skeleton10RThighSide': 'SkeletonRThighSide',
                        'Skeleton10RKneeOut': 'SkeletonRKneeOut',
                        'Skeleton10RShin': 'SkeletonRShin',
                        'Skeleton10RAnkleOut': 'SkeletonRAnkleOut',
                        'Skeleton10RToeTip': 'SkeletonRToeTip',
                        'Skeleton10RToeIn': 'SkeletonRToeIn',
                        'Skeleton10RToeOut': 'SkeletonRToeOut',
                        'Skeleton10RHeel': 'SkeletonRHeel',
                        'Skeleton10LThighFront': 'SkeletonLThighFront',
                        'Skeleton10LThighSide': 'SkeletonLThighSide',
                        'Skeleton10LKneeOut': 'SkeletonLKneeOut',
                        'Skeleton10LShin': 'SkeletonLShin',
                        'Skeleton10LAnkleOut': 'SkeletonLAnkleOut',
                        'Skeleton10LToeTip': 'SkeletonLToeTip',
                        'Skeleton10LToeIn': 'SkeletonLToeIn',
                        'Skeleton10LToeOut': 'SkeletonLToeOut',
                        'Skeleton10LHeel': 'SkeletonLHeel',

                        'Skeleton1ChestLow': 'SkeletonChestLow',
                        'Skeleton1ChestTop': 'SkeletonChestTop',
                        'Skeleton1WaistRFront': 'SkeletonWaistRFront',
                        'Skeleton1WaistLFront': 'SkeletonWaistLFront',
                        'Skeleton1WaistLBack': 'SkeletonWaistLBack',
                        'Skeleton1WaistRBack': 'SkeletonWaistRBack',
                        'Skeleton1WaistCBack': 'SkeletonWaistCBack',
                        'Skeleton1BackLeft': 'SkeletonBackLeft',
                        'Skeleton1BackRight': 'SkeletonBackRight',
                        'Skeleton1LShoulderBack': 'SkeletonLShoulderBack',
                        'Skeleton1RShoulderBack': 'SkeletonRShoulderBack',
                        'Skeleton1BackTop': 'SkeletonBackTop',
                        'Skeleton1HeadFront': 'SkeletonHeadFront',
                        'Skeleton1HeadTop': 'SkeletonHeadTop',
                        'Skeleton1HeadRight':'SkeletonHeadRight',
                        'Skeleton1HeadLeft': 'SkeletonHeadLeft',
                        'Skeleton1RShoulderTop': 'SkeletonRShoulderTop',
                        'Skeleton1RUArmHigh': 'SkeletonRUArmHigh',
                        'Skeleton1RElbowOut': 'SkeletonRElbowOut',
                        'Skeleton1RFArm': 'SkeletonRFArm',
                        'Skeleton1RWristIn': 'SkeletonRWristIn',
                        'Skeleton1RWristOut': 'SkeletonRWristOut',
                        'Skeleton1RHandIn': 'SkeletonRHandIn',
                        'Skeleton1RHandOut': 'SkeletonRHandOut',
                        'Skeleton1LShoulderTop': 'SkeletonLShoulderTop',
                        'Skeleton1LUArmHigh': 'SkeletonLUArmHigh',
                        'Skeleton1LElbowOut': 'SkeletonLElbowOut',
                        'Skeleton1LFArm': 'SkeletonLFArm',
                        'Skeleton1LWristIn': 'SkeletonLWristIn',
                        'Skeleton1LWristOut': 'SkeletonLWristOut',
                        'Skeleton1LHandIn': 'SkeletonLHandIn',
                        'Skeleton1LHandOut': 'SkeletonLHandOut',
                        'Skeleton1RThighFront': 'SkeletonRThighFront',
                        'Skeleton1RThighSide': 'SkeletonRThighSide',
                        'Skeleton1RKneeOut': 'SkeletonRKneeOut',
                        'Skeleton1RShin': 'SkeletonRShin',
                        'Skeleton1RAnkleOut': 'SkeletonRAnkleOut',
                        'Skeleton1RToeTip': 'SkeletonRToeTip',
                        'Skeleton1RToeIn': 'SkeletonRToeIn',
                        'Skeleton1RToeOut': 'SkeletonRToeOut',
                        'Skeleton1RHeel': 'SkeletonRHeel',
                        'Skeleton1LThighFront': 'SkeletonLThighFront',
                        'Skeleton1LThighSide': 'SkeletonLThighSide',
                        'Skeleton1LKneeOut': 'SkeletonLKneeOut',
                        'Skeleton1LShin': 'SkeletonLShin',
                        'Skeleton1LAnkleOut': 'SkeletonLAnkleOut',
                        'Skeleton1LToeTip': 'SkeletonLToeTip',
                        'Skeleton1LToeIn': 'SkeletonLToeIn',
                        'Skeleton1LToeOut': 'SkeletonLToeOut',
                        'Skeleton1LHeel': 'SkeletonLHeel',

                        'Skeleton6ChestLow': 'SkeletonChestLow',
                        'Skeleton6ChestTop': 'SkeletonChestTop',
                        'Skeleton6WaistRFront': 'SkeletonWaistRFront',
                        'Skeleton6WaistLFront': 'SkeletonWaistLFront',
                        'Skeleton6WaistLBack': 'SkeletonWaistLBack',
                        'Skeleton6WaistRBack': 'SkeletonWaistRBack',
                        'Skeleton6WaistCBack': 'SkeletonWaistCBack',
                        'Skeleton6BackLeft': 'SkeletonBackLeft',
                        'Skeleton6BackRight': 'SkeletonBackRight',
                        'Skeleton6LShoulderBack': 'SkeletonLShoulderBack',
                        'Skeleton6RShoulderBack': 'SkeletonRShoulderBack',
                        'Skeleton6BackTop': 'SkeletonBackTop',
                        'Skeleton6HeadFront': 'SkeletonHeadFront',
                        'Skeleton6HeadTop': 'SkeletonHeadTop',
                        'Skeleton6HeadRight':'SkeletonHeadRight',
                        'Skeleton6HeadLeft': 'SkeletonHeadLeft',
                        'Skeleton6RShoulderTop': 'SkeletonRShoulderTop',
                        'Skeleton6RUArmHigh': 'SkeletonRUArmHigh',
                        'Skeleton6RElbowOut': 'SkeletonRElbowOut',
                        'Skeleton6RFArm': 'SkeletonRFArm',
                        'Skeleton6RWristIn': 'SkeletonRWristIn',
                        'Skeleton6RWristOut': 'SkeletonRWristOut',
                        'Skeleton6RHandIn': 'SkeletonRHandIn',
                        'Skeleton6RHandOut': 'SkeletonRHandOut',
                        'Skeleton6LShoulderTop': 'SkeletonLShoulderTop',
                        'Skeleton6LUArmHigh': 'SkeletonLUArmHigh',
                        'Skeleton6LElbowOut': 'SkeletonLElbowOut',
                        'Skeleton6LFArm': 'SkeletonLFArm',
                        'Skeleton6LWristIn': 'SkeletonLWristIn',
                        'Skeleton6LWristOut': 'SkeletonLWristOut',
                        'Skeleton6LHandIn': 'SkeletonLHandIn',
                        'Skeleton6LHandOut': 'SkeletonLHandOut',
                        'Skeleton6RThighFront': 'SkeletonRThighFront',
                        'Skeleton6RThighSide': 'SkeletonRThighSide',
                        'Skeleton6RKneeOut': 'SkeletonRKneeOut',
                        'Skeleton6RShin': 'SkeletonRShin',
                        'Skeleton6RAnkleOut': 'SkeletonRAnkleOut',
                        'Skeleton6RToeTip': 'SkeletonRToeTip',
                        'Skeleton6RToeIn': 'SkeletonRToeIn',
                        'Skeleton6RToeOut': 'SkeletonRToeOut',
                        'Skeleton6RHeel': 'SkeletonRHeel',
                        'Skeleton6LThighFront': 'SkeletonLThighFront',
                        'Skeleton6LThighSide': 'SkeletonLThighSide',
                        'Skeleton6LKneeOut': 'SkeletonLKneeOut',
                        'Skeleton6LShin': 'SkeletonLShin',
                        'Skeleton6LAnkleOut': 'SkeletonLAnkleOut',
                        'Skeleton6LToeTip': 'SkeletonLToeTip',
                        'Skeleton6LToeIn': 'SkeletonLToeIn',
                        'Skeleton6LToeOut': 'SkeletonLToeOut',
                        'Skeleton6LHeel': 'SkeletonLHeel',

                        
                      }
